extreme: n.   极端
Lesson 5. The Facts. Editors of newspapers and magazines often go to extremes to provide their
第5课。事实。报纸和杂志的编辑经常去极端
statistics: n.   统计数字, journalist: n.   新闻记者
reader with unimportant. Facts and statistics. Last year a journalist had been instructed by a
读者不重要。事实和统计。去年，一位记者受到了
well-known magazine to write an article on the President's Palace in a New African Republic.
著名的杂志在新非洲共和国撰写了一篇有关总统宫殿的文章。
editor: n.   编辑, publish: v.   出版
When the article arrived, the editor read the first sentence and then refused to publish it.
当文章到达时，编辑会阅读第一句话，然后拒绝发布。
The article began. Hundreds of steps led to the high wall which surrounds the President's Palace.
文章开始。数百个步骤导致了围绕总统宫殿的高墙。
editor: n.   编辑, journalist: n.   新闻记者
The editor at once sent the journalist a facts instructing him find out the exact number of steps
编辑立即向记者发送了一个事实，指示他找出确切的步骤数量
journalist: n.   新闻记者
and the height of the wall. The journalist immediately set out to obtain these important facts,
和墙的高度。记者立即着手获得这些重要事实，
editor: n.   编辑, impatient: adj. 不耐烦的
but that took a long time to send them meanwhile. The editor was getting impatient. For the magazine
但这花了很长时间才寄给他们。编辑越来越不耐烦。对于杂志
journalist: n.   新闻记者, fax: n.   传真
would soon go to press. He sent the journalist two more faxes. But received no reply.
很快就会按下。他向记者发送了另外两个传真。但没有收到答复。
journalist: n.   新闻记者, fire: v.   解雇
He sent yet another facts informing the journalist that if he did not reply soon he would be fired.
他发出了另一个事实，告知记者，如果他不尽快回答，他将被解雇。
editor: n.   编辑, journalist: n.   新闻记者, publish: v.   出版
When the journalist again failed to reply, the editor reluctantly published the article as it
当记者再次没有回复时，编辑很不情愿地发表了文章
editor: n.   编辑, journalist: n.   新闻记者, originally: adv. 起初，原先，从前
had originally been written. A week later, the editor at last received a facts from the journalist
最初是写的。一周后，编辑终于收到了记者的事实
not only had the poor man been arrested, but he had been sent to prison as well. However,
穷人不仅被捕，而且他也被送进监狱。然而，
editor: n.   编辑
he had at last been allowed to send a facts in which he informed the editor that he had been
他终于被允许发送一个事实，他告诉编辑他曾经
arrested while counting the 1884 steps leading to the 15-foot wall which surrounded the
在计算1884年的台阶时被捕，通往周围的15英尺墙
President's Palace.
总统的宫殿。